#### Contact

janviermuhawenimana@gmail.c

www.linkedin.com/in/ muhawenimana-janvier-998842110 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Software System Analysis Graphic Design Web Design

# Muhawenimana janvier

Software Developer

Kigali

### Summary

Experienced Web Developer with a demonstrated history of working in the business supplies and equipment industry. Skilled in User Experience (UX), Software System Analysis, User Interface Design, Databases, Mobile Application development, and Graphic Design. Strong engineering professional

### Experience

Self-employed Web Developer January 2015 - Present (6 years 11 months) Rwanda

#### **THEPROGRESS**

Web Developer April 2017 - Present (4 years 8 months)

Progress tech
Prototype Designer and UX
January 2020 - 2020 (less than a year)
Rwanda

The PWS Africa Team Programming Workshop for Scientist in Africa 2020 - 2020 (less than a year) Kigali, Kigali City, Rwanda

Rwanda Basic Education Board
Dashboard and Data representation designer
2020 - 2020 (less than a year)
Kigali, Kigali City, Rwanda

I designed the dashboard (Statistics) user interface that represent the information in easy was and facilitate the decision making on TMIS (Teacher Management Information System)

#### Freelance

Mobile Application Developer January 2019 - 2019 (less than a year)

Rwanda

i build mobile application using react native

#### SOFTTECK Ltd

Design Mailing service on Umusanzu Wanjye Progect 2019 - 2019 (less than a year)

Kigali, Kigali City, Rwanda

Design Mailing service on Umusanzu Wanjye Progect to send notification on different events on the system

#### **ANTARES**

Information System design and management September 2016 - December 2018 (2 years 4 months)

Gisenyi, Western Province, Rwanda

Designed the Business solution (Information system) for ANTARES Information system which work in the intranet which manage their sells stock,... it is used in their daily services,

worked ANTARES company as a graphic designer and in sells.

#### ANTARES - Rwanda

Graphic Designer

September 2016 - January 2018 (1 year 5 months)

Gisenyi, Western Province, Rwanda

#### SHAMA SPRL

Web Developer

August 2017 - August 2017 (1 month)

Congo (DRC)

Information system/ web based internal system for SHAMA SPRL ink Company from Republic democratic of Congo

## Education

UNIVERSITY OF RWANDA

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science · (2018)